http://www.perpetualkid.com/privacy-policy/

Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment To PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available from each page on our website.
The Information We CollectThis notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the PerpetualKid.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
NameAddressEmail addressPhone numberCredit/Debit Card InformationI.P. Address(etc.)
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, additional types of personal information collected are:
Recipient's NameAddressPhone Number(etc.)
The Way We Use InformationWe use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order and provide you with order tracking. Such exceptions are for our shipping carrier and and reviews. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order. Email addresses are not used for any other purpose that corresponding with you, and are not sold to outside parties.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Anti-SpamWe hate Spam just as much as everybody else. We only send you emails to communicate about your order.
NewslettersIf you opt  to receive our email newsletters, you can easily unsubscribe at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the newsletter, emailing your request to customer-service@perpetualkid.com, or by sending a written request to Perpetual Kid, 42395 Ryan Road , Suite 112-102, Ashburn, VA 20148.
Opting OutIf you would like to unsubscribe to all correspondence with Perpetual Kid, please email customer-service@perpetualkid.com, or send a written request to Perpetual Kid, 42395 Ryan Road , Suite 112-102, Ashburn, VA 20148.
Our Commitment To Data SecurityTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children's PrivacyProtecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13.
×
OK
Newsletter Signup
Email Address
Brands
Blue Q
Fred & Friends- World Wide Fred
Archie McPhee
Whiskey River Soap Co.
